Digital Collections and Archives Records UA069
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Digital objects, 1662 -- 2015; 2000 -- 2004; UA069.005; 542 Digital Object(s)
  - First Glance at BOP Program is Fine, But Administration's Borrowing Time, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00360; Wriston, Walter B.
    Balance of payments United States; Investments, Foreign; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Doing Business in an Age of Electronic Miracles and Wonder, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00361; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Doing Business in an Age of Electronic Miracles and Wonder," written by Walter B. Wriston for the June 22, 1987 edition of "American Banker." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00002.
  - Was I exacting? Sure. Was I occasionally sarcastic? Of course., 2007; UA069.005.DO.00362; Wriston, Walter B.
    This document was created from the article, "Was I exacting? Sure. Was I occasionally sarcastic? Of course." written by Walter B. Wriston for the June 1987 edition of "Institutional Investor." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00001.
    Banks and banking; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Visions 2000, 2007; UA069.005.DO.00363
    This document was created from the article, "Visions 2000." written by an unknown author for the November/December 1991 edition of "Chief Executive." The original article is located in MS134.003.027.00017.
    Interviews; Business; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Risk & Other Four-Letter Words, 1986; UA069.005.DO.00364; Wriston, Walter B.
    Risk & Other Four-Letter Words is a compilation of speeches by Walter B. Wriston discussing information technology and economics.
    Information technology; Economics.; Wriston, Walter B.; Harper & Row Publishers
    - Risk & Other Four-Letter Words book jacket, 1986; UA069.005.DO.00364.00001; Wriston, Walter B.
      This image is the front cover of the book jacket for the publication, "Risk & Other Four-Letter Words."
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office at Citicorp Center after his retirement, 1984, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00365
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'File2645' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4' located in MS134.006.036.00004 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.
  - Back Row: Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston) Front Row: Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister); Ruth Bigelow Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's mother); and Walter B. Wriston during Henry Merritt Wriston's presidency at Lawrence University (Appleton, Wisconsin), 1925, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00366
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2816' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow
  - Left to Right: Paul W. McCracken, Alan Greenspan, President Ronald Reagan, George P. Shultz, and Walter B. Wriston during a meeting of the Economic Policy Advisory Board in the Oval Office, 1981, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00367
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph 21' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; McCracken, Paul W.; Greenspan, Alan; Reagan, Ronald; Shultz, George P.
  - Walter B. Wriston during his tenure as editor of the 'Argosy' (Wesleyan University's student newspaper) and Barbara Brengle, 1938-1940, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00368
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2809' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Barbara Brengle
  - Walter B. Wriston in his army uniform during World War II at his grandparent's (Henry Lincoln Wriston and Jennie Atcheson Wriston) home in Manhattan, NY, 1943-1944, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00369
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2808' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
  - Left to Right: Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister), Jennie Atcheson Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandmother), Walter B. Wriston, and Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife), 1940s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00370
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2807' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Jennie Atcheson; Wriston, Barbara Brengle; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston at Citicorp/Citigroup, 1980s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00371
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'File2646' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4' located in MS134.006.036.00004 box number 39090014014514.
  - Left to Right: Colin Campbell, President of Wesleyan; Senator Edward M. Kennedy, David McCullough; Natalie Zemon Davis; Walter B. Wriston; Nicholas John Turro, Jr.; and D. Ronald Daniel, Board Chairman of Wesleyan University Trustees, June 3, 1984, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00372
    The image was created from 'File2800' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514
    Wriston, Walter B.; Campbell, Colin; Kennedy, Edward M.; McCullough, David; Davis, Natalie Zemon; Turro, Nicholas John Jr.; Daniel, D. Ronald
  - Left to Right: Ruth Bigelow Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's mother), Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father), Barbara Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's sister), Walter B. Wriston, and Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife) during Henry Merritt Wriston's presidency at Brown University, 1944, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00373
    The image was created from 'File2821' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2' located in MS134.006.036.00002 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Ruth Bigelow; Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Barbara; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Barbara Brengle
  - Henry Lincoln Wriston and, his wife, Jennie Atcheson Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandparents), 1940s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00374
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2811' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Henry Lincoln; Wriston, Jennie Atcheson
  - Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father) on his wedding day to Marguerite Woodsworth, June 28, 1947, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00375
    The image was created from 'File2815' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Henry Merritt; Woodsworth, Marguerite
  - Barbara Brengle Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife) holding Catherine Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's daughter), Winter 1948, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00376
    The image was created from 'File2813' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Barbara Brengle; Quintal, Catherine Wriston
  - Walter B. Wriston with his daughter, Catherine, on her wedding day to Richard Quintal in the Church of Heavenly Rest (New York, N.Y.), August 7, 1971, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00377
    The image was created from 'File2803' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Catherine Wriston
  - Walter B. Wriston with his grandson, Christopher W. Quintal, in his office in Citicorp Center, 1984, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00378
    The image was created from 'File3122' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 6' located in MS134.006.036.00006 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Christopher W.
  - Walter B. Wriston with his granddaughter, Barbara Catherine Quintal, on the Wriston farm in Connecticut, 1994, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00379
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File3123' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 6' located in MS134.006.036.00006 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine
  - Left to Right: Walter B. Wriston; Barbara Catherine Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's granddaughter); Christopher W. Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's grandson); Catherine Wriston Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's daughter); Richard Quintal (Walter B. Wriston's son-in-law) In front: Kathryn Dineen Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's wife), 1999, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00380
    The image was created from 'File2802' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Christopher W.; Quintal, Catherine Wriston; Quintal, Richard; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen
  - Walter B. Wriston on his wedding day to Kathryn Dineen in St. Ignatius Loyola Roman Catholic Church, March 14, 1968, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00381
    This image is copyrighted to the 'New York Times.' The image was created from 'File2804' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514. Behind the couple are Reverend Robert Haskins and Henry Merritt Wriston, also present is Carolyn B. Dineen Randall (Kathryn Dineen Wriston's sister).
    Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen
  - Thomas Creamer (Citicorp/Citigroup), Walter B. Wriston (Citicorp/Citigroup), and Reverend Ralph E. Peterson (St. Peter's Church) at the groundbreaking for Citicorp Center, 1972, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00382
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citigroup. The image was created from 'File2824' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3' located in MS134.006.036.00003 box number 39090014014514.
    Creamer, Thomas; Wriston, Walter B.; Peterson, Ralph E.
  - Walter B. Wriston and his wife, Kathryn, in Florida, 1990s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00383
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2801' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston in his early years at First National City Bank, 1950s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00384
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2822' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3' located in MS134.006.036.00003 box number 39090014014514.
  - President John F. Kennedy, Walter B. Wriston, and other members of the Task Force on International Investment, Summer 1963, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00385
    The image was created from 'File2905' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5' located in MS134.006.036.00005 box number 39090014014514.
    Kennedy, John F.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston, President Richard M. Nixon, and other members of the National Commission on Productivity in The White House Cabinet Room, 1970-1974, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00386
    This date is approximate. The image was created from '07082210450_1' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5' located in MS134.006.036.00005 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-
  - Walter B. Wriston and President Gerald R. Ford, 1974-1977, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00387
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2806' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Ford, Gerald R.
  - Walter B. Wriston being sworn in as Chairman of President Ronald Reagan's Economic Advisory Board with George P. Shultz in attendance, March 1982, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00388
    The image was created from 'File2805' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Shultz, George P.
  - President Ronald Reagan, Walter B. Wriston, and other members of the Economic Policy Committee in the White House Roosevelt Room, 1981-1989, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00389
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2906' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5' located in MS134.006.036.00005 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Reagan, Ronald
  - Walter B. Wriston and Laurent Jacque, Chair of International Business Relations, December 18, 2003, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00390
    Laurent Jacque is Director of the International Business Relations Program at the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy and the Walter B. Wriston Professor of International Business.
    Wriston, Walter B.; Jacque, Laurent L.
  - Walter B. Wriston after his retirement from Citibank/Citicorp, 1990s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00391
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'File2644' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4' located in MS134.006.036.00004 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston, 1980s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00392
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'File2647' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 4' located in MS134.006.036.00004 box number 39090014014514.
  - Henry Merritt Wriston and, his wife, Ruth Bigelow Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's parents), 1930s-1940s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00393
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2812' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Henry Merritt; Wriston, Ruth Bigelow
  - Walter B. Wriston with his daughter, Catherine, in front of the Statue of Liberty, 1954, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00394
    The image was created from 'File2814' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 1' located in MS134.006.036.00001 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston at eleven years old in Appleton, Wisconsin, July 1931, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00395
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2817' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2' located in MS134.006.036.00002 box number 39090014014514.
  - Left to Right: Henry Lincoln Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's grandfather), Walter B. Wriston, and Henry Merritt Wriston (Walter B. Wriston's father) at Walter B. Wriston's wedding to Barbara Brengle in Scarsdale, New York, October 24, 1942, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00396
    The image was created from 'File2820' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 2' located in MS134.006.036.00002 box number 39090014014514. Henry Lincoln Wriston performed the marriage ceremony of Walter B. Wriston and Barbara Brengle.
    Wriston, Henry Lincoln; Wriston, Walter B.; Wriston, Henry Merritt
  - Walter B. Wriston shaking hands with President Ronald Reagan, ca. 1981-1989, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00397
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2825' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3' located in MS134.006.036.00003 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston, a year after graduating from Appleton High School, 1938, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00398
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2826' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 3' located in MS134.006.036.00003 box number 39090014014514.
  - President George H.W. Bush and Walter B. Wriston in the Vice President's Office in the White House, 1989-1993, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00399
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'File2908' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 5' located in MS134.006.036.00005 box number 39090014014514.
    Bush, George H.W.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - George S. Moore, Chairman of First National City Bank and Walter B. Wriston, President and CEO of First National City Bank, 1967, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00400
    This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'L1000007' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Moore, George S.; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston and his wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, early 2000s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00401
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (2)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston and, his second wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, ca. 1970s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00402
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (10)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office at 399 Park Ave, NY as Chairman and CEO of Citibank and Citigroup, 1970s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00403
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'Photograph (16)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
  - Walter B. Wriston in his office at Citibank during his term as Chairman of Citibank/Citigroup (an image of Thomas Gresham on the wall), early 1980s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00404
    This date is approximate. This image is copyrighted to Citicorp/Citigroup. The image was created from 'Photograph (18)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
  - David F. Linowes, Chairman of President Reagan's Commission on Privitization, Walter B. Wriston, and Richard H. Fink at a meeting of the Commission of Privitization, ca. 1987, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00405
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (20)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Linowes, David F.; Wriston, Walter B.; Fink, Richard H.
  - George P. Shultz, Walter B. Wriston, Unidentified Man, Unidentified Man, Unidentified Man, Paul McCracken, Alan Greenspan, and Unidentified Man, 1980s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00406
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (22)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Shultz, George P.; Wriston, Walter B.; McCracken, Paul W.; Greenspan, Alan
  - Back Row: Kathryn Dineen Wriston, Walter B. Wriston, and Christopher W. Quintal Front Row: Barbara Catherine 'Katy' Quintal, Richard Quintal, and Catherine Wriston Quintal, mid-1990s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00407
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (27)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Wriston, Kathryn Dineen; Wriston, Walter B.; Quintal, Christopher W.; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Richard; Quintal, Catherine Wriston
  - Left to Right: Christopher W. Quintal, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, Catherine Wriston Quintal holding Barbara Catherine 'Katy' Quintal, Richard Quintal, and Walter B. Wriston, 1989, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00408
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (32)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
    Quintal, Christopher W.; Wriston, Kathryn Dineen; Quintal, Catherine Wriston; Quintal, Barbara Catherine; Quintal, Richard; Wriston, Walter B.
  - Walter B. Wriston and his wife, Kathryn Dineen Wriston, early 1990s, 2008; UA069.005.DO.00409
    This date is approximate. The image was created from 'Photograph (34)' from the CD titled 'Walter B. Wriston Photographs - CD 7' located in MS134.006.036.00007 box number 39090014014514.
  - Policies and procedures, 1998 -- 2008; UA069.005.00001; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 276 files.; 34 Megabytes
  - Nils hopper dump, 1995 -- 2008; UA069.005.00002; 7 Digital Object(s) 7 digital objects comprising 165,724 files.; 22.4 Gigabytes
  - Bookmark files (Boston Streets and Tufts History), 2004; UA069.005.00003; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 55 files.; 86 Megabytes
  - Bookmark files (V-12), 2003 -- 2006; UA069.005.00004; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 29 files.; 20 Megabytes
  - Forest Web Pages, 2007; UA069.005.00005; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 538 files.; 120 Megabytes
  - DCA Director's email, 2007 -- 2008; UA069.005.00006; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 2 files.; 144 Megabytes
    For internal staff use only.
  - Files from Q drive re: TDL and website, 2003 -- 2012; UA069.005.00007; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 1,691 files.; 117 Megabytes
  - Accessioning P and Ps, 2005 -- 2007; UA069.005.00008; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 16 files.; 1 Megabytes
  - Digital photos including commencement 2013, 2013-05-19; UA069.005.00009; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 4 files.; 5 Megabytes
  - Record Archivist digital files, 2006 -- 2013; UA069.005.00010; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 77 files.; 119 Megabytes
    Records closed 20 years from date of creation. Email is for internal staff use only.
  - Q-cleanup accessions, 1999 -- 2015; UA069.005.00011; 3 Digital Object(s) 3 digital objects comprising 9,565 files.; 8.7 Gigabytes
    These transfer_bags are from the Q-cleanup project undertaken by Erin Faulder, Archivist for Digital Collections, in March, 2015. Transfer bags are labeled according to original folder structure in Q.
    Departmental_Project_workspace_transferBag; Disaster_plan_transferBag; frontdesk_transferBag; Gill_project_transferBag; Holmes_transferBag; Minutes_transferBag; Pending_Rejected_grant_applications_transferBag; Procedures_transferBag; Project_grant_administration_transferBag; Records_creator_project; Records_keeping_sys_requirements_transferBag; Repository_DL_technical_map_transferBag; Service_level_agreements_transferBag; students_and_interns_transferBag; TDL_web_template_transferBag; temp_images_transferBag; web_mirror_2007_transferBag; wiki_download_transferBag; Winter_card_2008_transferBag; Xythos_transferBag
  - Staff presentations, 2004 -- 2006; UA069.005.00012; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 10 files.; 15 Megabytes
    DCA staff presentations (slides) from regional, national, and international professional conferences,
  - Archivist for Digital Collections' emails, 2013 -- 2015; UA069.005.00013; 1 Digital Object(s) 1 digital object comprising 8 files.; 141 Megabytes
    Contains emails documenting CIDER development, Hydra Development, ETD policy development, FROG planning, HHSL slide scanning project, Sudan Peace Project processing, Fletcher white papers documentation project, and Carthage digitization project.
  - Web materials, 1998; UA069.000839; 1 Digital Object(s) One zip file comprising 653 files.; 191 Megabytes
    Zip file of web files stored in the dark archive and can be made available upon request. Access and playback is difficult without emulation services.
    Files used to build an older version of the DCA website.
- Exhibit-related materials, 1940 -- 2013; 2005 -- 2007; UA069.007; 7.75 Linear Feet
  This series contains exhibit materials including mounted photos, artifacts, and labels created by Digital Collections and Archives staff.
  This series is arranged chronologically by date of exhibit.
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [1 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Tufts College: A Wartime Campus [2 of 6], 2000 -- 2001; UA069.007.001.00002 (Box 1)